Chris Tsoukaladelis

https://tsoukaladelis.xyz ctsoukaladel@cs.stonybrook.edu

About Me

I'm currently a PhD candidate at Stony Brook University, where I work with Prof. Nick Nikiforakis in the PragSec lab. My main areas of interest is web integrity and transparency, and orthogonally I do research on system isolation-based security and web application debloating. I am passionate about privacy, anonymity and freedom on the web.

Publications

 The Times, They Are A-Changin': Characterizing Post-Publication Changes to Online News

(To appear) IEEE Symposium on Security and Privacy 2024

AnimateDead: Debloating Web Applications Using Concolic Execution
Usenix Security 2023

Education

Stony Brook University

2021 - Present

PhD Candidate

University of Patras

2014 - 2020

Engineer's Degree (BS+MS equivalent) in electrical and computer engineering

Experience

Stony Brook University

2021 - Present

Research Assistant

 PragSec lab: My main focus is on web content integrity and transparency. Orthogonally, I have worked on web application debloating and other areas of web security.

Virginia Commonwealth University

2020 - 2021

Research Assistant

 MHRG lab: I developed techniques for both intrusion detection, as well as penetration of SCADA systems.

University of Patras

2017 - 2020

Research Assistant

 Computer Systems lab: I worked on developing and maintaining a malware detection and classification platform.
I also participated in various online capture the flag (CtF) competitions.

Datawise Data Engineering LLC

2018 - 2020

DevOps, Security Consultant

 Security Consultant: I was a consultant for various security decisions made in the handling of sensitive data, ranging from credit card information to ancient artifacts from the Acropolis museum.

Skills

- o Programming Python, C/C++, Go, PHP, Javascript, Bash, x86 ASM
- System administration Linux, openBSD
- Web application debloating, sandboxing
- o Browser automation
- o Bot automation & analysis of anti-bot mechanisms
- Data Analysis R, Machine Learning